# MOGBOLU, Vivian Ijeoma



0816-9240-331, 0818-1540-376



vivianmogbolu2020@gmail.c



3, Association Street, Ashi-Bodija, Ibadan, Oyo State.

## Skills

- + Time Management
- + Telephone call handling
- + Excellent numerical skills
- + Good communication skills (both written and oral)
- + Client Liaison
- + Transaction Processing
- + Effective research and reporting skills
- + Statistical Data Analysis

#### I.T SKILLS

Microsoft Office, R Language, SPSS, Oxmetrics, Latex and Beamer

## **EDUCATION**

University of Ibadan, Oyo State

+ MSc Statistics - In View

### University of Ibadan, Oyo State

+ BSc (Hons) Statistics (First Class) 2015 - 2018

The Polytechnic, Ibadan, Oyo State

+ National Diploma (N.D) (Distinction) **Mathematics and Statistics** 

2011 - 2013

#### Methodist Grammar School, Ibadan, Oyo State

+ West African Senior School Certificate 2002 - 2008

## CERTIFICATES

- + Certificate of Excellence, National Mathematical Competition, Abuja.
- + Best Graduating Student (2012/2013), Department of Mathematics and Statistics, The Polytechnic, Ibadan
- + Certificate of Presentation, 4th International Conference on Scientific Research in Nigeria, University of Ibadan.
- + Deputy Cadet-in-Chief NYSC Road Safety Club, Kebbi State Command

## Personal Profile

A competent statistician and an enthusiastic administrator with experience of working as part of teams in achieving desired goals.

Well organized, trustworthy, efficient, personable and proactive in providing timely and consistently high results even in challenging and pressurized work environments.

## **Work Experience**

## J-Rapha Hospital and Maternity Ltd, Ibadan, Oyo State

Administrative/Cash Control Officer

2013 - 2015

#### **Duties**

- + Daily and monthly analysis with full report of flow of income and expenditure.
- + Typing documents and distributing memos.
- + Cash and Cheque payment into the bank.
- + Handling incoming / outgoing calls, correspondence and filing.
- + Clients and staff records keeping.
- + Monitoring inventory, office stock and ordering supplies as necessary.
- + Updating & maintaining the leave, absence and training records of staff.
- + Creating and modifying documents using Microsoft Office and
- + Setting up and coordinating meetings.
- + Updating, processing and filing of all documents.

## Genius Information Technology, Ibadan, Oyo State

## Secretary

2009 - 2011

### **Duties**

- + Registration and documentation of clients' services.
- + Clients training.
- + Creating and modifying documents using Microsoft Office.
- + Updating, processing and filing of all documents.